《行尸走肉》前情提要
Previously, on AMC's, "The Walking Dead."
一顆子彈解決不了任何問題
A single bullet ain't gonna do it.
給我做一顆子彈
Make me a bullet.
有人會付出代價的
Somebody has to pay the price.
這是什么
What is this?
這玩意是手工做出來的嗎
This little bad boy made from scratch.
告訴我是誰做的
You tell me who made this.
快走
求求你  不要
Please. Please don't.
天啊  不要
Please, god, no.
我討厭這樣  求你了
I hate this. Please!
m 211 -8 b 217 -6 217 -4 217 -2 l 217 24 b 217 26 217 29 211 31 l 31 31 b 26 29 26 26 26 24 l 26 -2 b 26 -4 26 -6 31 -8
m 20 0 l 209 0 b 218 0 229 11 229 20 l 229 209 b 229 218 218 228 209 228 l 20 228 b 11 228 0 218 0 209 l 0 20 b 0 11 11 0 20 0
m 115 64 l 115 35 l 171 0 l 177 0 l 133 46 l 143 52 l 179 0 l 184 0 l 159 63 l 229 107 l 229 182 l 145 96 l 135 122 l 207 227 l 137 227 l 115 172 l 115 93 l 126 76 l 115 64 l 104 76 l 115 93 l 115 172 l 93 227 l 23 227 l 95 122 l 84 96 l 0 182 l 0 107 l 70 63 l 45 0 l 50 0 l 87 52 l 97 46 l 52 0 l 59 0 l 115 35
m 71 60 b 71 0 161 0 161 60 b 161 120 71 120 71 60
m 325 0 l 355 0 l 332 47 l 354 47 l 399 136 l 369 136 l 328 53 l 288 136 l 257 136 l 325 0 m 467 0 l 497 0 l 474 47 l 496 47 l 541 136 l 511 136 l 470 53 l 430 136 l 399 136 l 467 0 m 545 1 l 583 1 l 583 14 l 568 14 l 568 19 l 583 19 l 583 30 l 568 30 l 568 34 l 599 34 l 599 30 l 583 30 l 583 19 l 599 19 l 599 14 l 583 14 l 583 1 l 611 1 b 616 1 622 6 622 10 l 622 36 l 652 0 l 678 0 l 644 41 l 622 41 l 622 47 l 596 47 l 597 54 l 625 54 l 625 68 l 541 68 l 541 54 l 572 54 l 571 47 l 545 47 l 545 1 m 583 72 l 583 85 l 569 85 l 569 90 l 598 90 l 598 85 l 583 85 l 583 72 l 611 72 b 615 72 621 78 621 82 l 653 44 l 678 44 l 644 86 l 621 86 l 621 103 l 597 103 l 597 136 l 570 136 l 564 126 l 562 136 l 542 136 l 548 107 l 568 107 l 565 121 l 571 121 l 571 103 l 547 103 l 547 72 l 583 72 m 600 107 l 620 107 l 624 124 l 653 89 l 679 89 l 642 136 l 615 136 l 618 132 l 606 132 l 600 107 m 689 0 l 716 0 l 721 15 l 732 15 l 732 30 l 718 56 l 731 56 l 735 100 l 721 100 l 717 59 l 714 64 l 714 136 l 693 136 l 693 79 l 676 79 l 707 30 l 679 30 l 679 15 l 694 15 l 689 0 m 738 0 l 804 0 b 807 0 813 6 813 9 l 813 87 l 794 87 l 794 14 l 756 14 l 756 87 l 763 77 l 763 21 l 787 21 l 787 91 l 798 91 l 798 120 l 820 120 l 812 136 l 778 136 l 778 90 l 748 136 l 723 136 l 756 87 l 738 87 l 738 0 m 257 151 l 275 151 l 297 182 l 319 151 l 337 151 l 304 197 l 304 227 l 290 227 l 290 197 l 257 151 m 337 151 l 355 151 l 377 182 l 399 151 l 417 151 l 384 197 l 384 227 l 370 227 l 370 197 l 337 151 m 425 192 l 447 192 b 445 181 427 181 425 192 l 410 192 b 414 162 458 162 462 192 l 462 206 l 425 206 b 425 210 429 212 433 213 l 462 213 l 462 227 l 433 227 b 412 227 408 203 410 192 m 462 151 l 532 151 l 532 165 l 504 165 l 504 227 l 489 227 l 489 165 l 462 165 l 462 151 m 580 172 l 580 186 l 549 186 b 543 186 543 192 549 192 l 565 192 b 589 192 589 227 565 227 l 532 227 l 532 213 l 565 213 b 570 213 570 206 565 206 l 549 206 b 524 206 524 172 549 172 l 580 172 m 592 213 l 606 213 l 606 227 l 592 227 l 592 213 m 639 172 l 665 172 l 665 186 l 639 186 b 623 186 623 213 639 213 l 665 213 l 665 227 l 639 227 b 603 227 603 172 639 172 m 700 184 b 722 184 722 215 700 215 l 700 229 b 740 229 740 170 700 170 b 660 170 660 229 700 229 l 700 215 b 680 215 680 184 700 184 m 737 172 l 782 172 b 803 172 813 177 813 198 l 813 228 l 799 228 l 799 198 b 799 186 793 187 782 187 l 782 228 l 768 228 l 768 187 l 752 187 l 752 228 l 737 228 l 737 172
原創翻譯  雙語字幕
最新連載海外影視劇下載
請登陸 www.YYeTs.com
僅供交流學習  禁止商用盈利
m 38 -1 l 44 6 l 38 13 l 19 13 b 14 12 14 6 14 6 b 14 6 14 0 19 -1
m 200 -1 l 200 13 l 19 13 b 14 12 14 6 14 6 b 14 6 14 0 19 -1
翻譯     冰藍 Reginamoon CS小明漫畫家
翻譯     小酸奶 蘑菇 小僵僵 送小孩
校對     送小孩
時間軸     某雪  加森  濤濤
后期     送小哥  拉圖
總監     送小孩
歡迎回家  長毛
Welcome home, haircut.
圖書館還有更多的書
There's more at the library.
多得多
A lot more.
你們
You, uh...
你們有圖書館嗎
You have a library?
你朋友達里爾
Your friend Daryl
離開之前沒機會看到
didn't get a chance to see it before he bounced.
他逃跑了嗎
He escaped?
是的
Yeah.
你知道他在哪嗎
You know where he is?
不知道
No.
如果我知道  我會告訴你的
I'd tell you if I did.
《旺達·N· 麥金太爾》
Vonda N. Mcintyre.
這本就行了
Th-this will be satisfactory.
你餓了嗎
You hungry?
我給你弄點吃的  你想要什么
I'll get you something. What do you want?
我想要什么
What do I want?
是啊  吃什么  你想要什么
Yeah, to eat. What do you want?
什么都可以嗎
Anything?
是啊  隨便
Sure. Whatever.
真的嗎  我想要什么都行
Really? Anything I want?
哥們  是的
Dude, yes.
想吃什么都行  你想吃什么
You can have anything. What do you want?
-我能吃龍蝦嗎  -不行
- Can I have lobster? - No, you can't have lobster.
你他媽以為這是什么地方
What the hell do you think this is?
有罐頭意面和番茄醬嗎
Do you have canned pasta and tomato sauce?
你想要橙色的還是紅色的
You want orange-y or red?
橙色的
Orange-y.
好
All right.
有腌黃瓜嗎  我愛吃腌黃瓜
What about pickles? I-I like pickles.
我們沒腌黃瓜了
We're out of pickles.
那薯片呢
What about potato chips?
我們有薯片
We got chips.
42號做的
Number 42 makes them.
42號是這里人的代碼系統嗎
Number 42 is a coding system for persons here?
是工人的
For the workers, yeah.
他們做的是新鮮薯片嗎
They make said chips fresh?
是啊  他們有個壺
Yeah, they got a kettle --
不用了  謝謝
No, thanks.
好  我十分鐘后回來
Okay. I'll be back in 10.
享受你的新地方吧
Enjoy your new place.
快走
行尸走肉
『第七季  第十一集』
早上好  小子
Good mornin', sunshine.
這和你回憶中的一樣舒適嗎
Is it just as cozy as you remember?
你跟你妻子和蒂娜去愚蠢的自駕游之后
You spent a lot of time on the wrong side of the door
就花了許多時間待在門的錯誤一邊
after that stupid road trip with the wife and Tina.
我們現在談談吧
So let's talk about now.
我們在邊界周圍花了幾個小時
We went out looking for your little failed project
尋找你的失敗項目
for a few hours, just around the perimeter --
從頭到尾找了一遍
Tip to taint, as it were --
就在我讓人把你扔進這里的時候
right about the time I had you thrown in here,
我回來后
and when I got back,
意識到自己
I realized I...
少了個
was short...
妻子
a wife.
哪個
Which one?
雪莉
Sherry.
你知道些什么嗎  小德
You know anything about that, Dwighty boy?
因為我得告訴你
'cause I got to tell you,
這真他媽太巧了
that is one hell of a coincidence,
達里爾走后幾小時  她就離開了
her leaving just a few short hours after Daryl took off.
他根本沒有靠武力打出去
Oh, and he didn't force his way out.
沒有
No.
有人為他開門了
Somebody opened the door for him.
不是雪莉
It wasn't Sherry.
小德
Dwighty boy...
是你嗎
Was it you?
事情往反方向發展了嗎
Did it work the other way around?
你本該擊潰他的
You were supposed to break him.
他把你感化了嗎
Did he break you?
實話實說
I mean, let's face it --
你有一些合理的不滿
You've got some pretty legitimate grievances.
你背叛我了嗎  德懷特
You change your stripes on me, Dwighty?
你開始有不同的想法了嗎
You startin' to see things different?
經歷了這么多
After all this...
之前和之后
Before and after...
該死  經歷了這么多之后
Hell, after everything...
你到底是誰  德懷特
...Who are you, Dwight?
我是尼根
I'm Negan.
達里爾和你不一樣
Daryl isn't like you.
他
He's...
有感情
Emotional.
所以他要么在回家的路上
So he's either on his way home,
要么在回這里的路上
Or he's coming back here
試圖多殺我們幾個人
to try to kill some more of us.
主要是殺你和我
Mostly you and me.
無論怎樣  我們都會找到他
Either way, we'll find him.
所以...
So...
你知道雪莉去哪了嗎
do you think you know where Sherry went?
知道
Yeah.
把她帶回來
Bring her back.
解決這事
Sort it out.
給他縫縫針
Stitch him up.
把能治的地方都治一治
Fix what you can fix.
你不認為是她做的嗎
You don't think she did it?
你覺得是她做的嗎
You think she did?
我對她有些了解
I got to know her a little bit.
雖然不是很了解
Not well.
但足以想明白是怎么回事了
Well enough to know what happened.
她看見達里爾當時的處境
She saw Daryl in here, in the state he was in.
就把他放走了
She let him go.
她心軟
She was soft.
很善良
She has a big heart.
你被打了一頓扔進牢里...
You were just beaten and thrown in a cell --
要我說的話很冤
unfairly, if you ask me.
而你跟沒事人似的
And you're back to it.
說不定你以后會為他掌管一個哨站
You may wind up running an outpost for him.
你懂的
You get it.
我覺得我也懂
I like to think that I do.
那種無私  溫柔
The type of selfless, tender soul
愿意嫁給尼根以救自己丈夫一命的人
who would marry Negan to save her husband's life?
也正是不應該...
That's exactly the kind of person who really isn't...
活到現在的人
expected to be around anymore.
謝了
Thanks.
只是想幫幫忙而已
Just trying to help.
這里有大家種植的  制造的
Stuff people grow, stuff people make,
以及搜刮的東西
stuff, you know, people scavenge.
啤酒  面包  剪頭
Beer, bread, cut your head.
剪什么
Cut your what?
理發師
Barber.
也許能拯救一下你頭上那坨東西
Might be able to kill that thing on your head.
我們用的是工分系統
We use a points system.
你現在是我們中的一員了  和他們不一樣
You're one of us now, not them.
他們伙食糟糕  我們吃香喝辣
They eat shit, we eat good.
寫下你拿了什么  或者讓他們做了什么
Write what you took or what they did,
然后寫上對應的分數  再簽個名
how much it was worth, sign your name.
就這么簡單
That's it.
今天一定是你的幸運日  長毛
Must be your lucky day, haircut.
這些是自家做的嗎
Are these homemade?
是的
Yeah.
真是不錯的手工腌菜
That's some good DIY stuff there.
不...不用了  謝謝
No -- no, thank you.
你想要什么
You want something...
就拿什么  長毛
you take it, haircut.
我們讓西蒙過去看一眼
We'll send Simon over to take a peak,
先來軟的
sort of good-cop this thing first,
看看有什么效果
see how far we get.
他來了
There he is.
全場焦點
Man of the hour!
過來  大塊頭
Come on over here, big fella.
別這么沒禮貌  混蛋
Don't be rude, asshole.
說"你好"啊
Say hello.
你...好
H-h-hello.
你有名字嗎  混蛋
You got a name, asshole?
尤金
Eugene.
輪到我們了
Now us.
你是誰
Who are you?
我是尼根
I'm Negan.
尤金...
Well, Eugene...
我知道你還記得露西爾
I know you remember Lucille.
你看見這里這個東西了嗎
Now, you see this right here?
你可能得靠近點仔細看看
You might have to get real close.
我的朋友  那是你造的子彈
That, my friend, is the bullet you made.
在正常情況下
Now, under normal circumstances,
我會一遍又一遍地讓你親密接觸它
I'd be showing you that real close over and over again.
但是  尤金  你瞧
But, Eugene, see,
我只想知道你是不是個機靈鬼
all I really want to know is if you are a smarty-pants.
你懂的很多嗎
You know things?
回答我
Answer the question.
我...我確實挺機靈的
I -- I am, indeed, a smarty-pants.
我...自學了造子彈
I...taught myself to cast bullets.
我...找到了一個...
I...found a --
找到了一個機械車間
found a machine shop
那里有必需的...
with the necessary...
我讀了很多書...
I-I read a lot, and, um...
盡管我...
although my --
盡管我做不到過目不忘
Even though my memory is not considered eidetic,
但我也不會走馬觀花
I don't skim and I don't scrimp.
假如書上有什么知識
If knowledge is dropped,
我就會學會
I do, indeed, pick it up.
你真的只是個混蛋而已
Oh, you really are just some asshole.
不  我不是
N-no. I'm not.
我有好幾個生物化學
I have PHDs in biochemistry,
以及免疫學與微生物學博士學位
as well as immunology and microbiology,
我完成了博士學業  是貨真價實的博士
and I've completed my doctorate, which makes me a doctor.
S05E01中尤金曾撒過同樣的謊
災變之前
Prior to the collapse,
我是人類基因組計劃十人小組的成員
I was part of a 10-person team at the human genome project,
受布魯克斯·埃利斯博士領導
working under Dr. T. Brooks Ellis
研制對抗病毒武器的病毒武器
to weaponize diseases to fight weaponized diseases.
以毒...攻毒
Fire with, uh... You know...fire.
不同部門間喝過酒...
Well, see, interdepartmental drinks were --
好吧  機靈鬼博士
All right, Dr. Smarty-pants.
你應該能不費吹灰之力解決這事
You ought to be able to crack this without breaking a sweat.
你看  圍欄邊我有很多免費勞工
You see, I have a lot of free labor here at the fence,
活死人可以防止其他雜碎進來
living dead pricks that help keep the riffraff out.
問題是它們站不住  總會散架
Problem is, they don't keep. They fall apart.
就像那攤可憐的
Like that poor sack of...
狗屎玩意
pile of shit there.
所以  機靈鬼博士
So, Dr. Smarty-Pants,
怎么才能讓它們站住
How do we keep them on their feet?
你們
You, um...
經常冶煉  對嗎
smelt on the regs, correct?
我看到一堆遺留設備當中
I saw that among the legacy equipment on the floor that
-有可運作的熔爐  -是又怎樣
- you possess an operational smelter.  - And?
你們已經掌握了解決問題的辦法
You already possess the means to resolve your issue.
第一步  熔化金屬廢料
Step one, melt down scrap metal.
第二步  鐵鏈拴住行尸
Step two, pour it over the compromised walker
把金屬液澆到它們身上
as they are in contact with the chain link.
液態金屬會變硬
The liquid metal will harden...
既可以保持行尸身體完整
Both maintaining bodily integrity for the walker
又可以把它們粘在圍欄上
as well as affixing them to the fence.
更棒的是遮蓋了它們的頭部
Bonus points for covering their head
防止敵人攻擊或意外導致腦袋碎裂
and protecting them from head trauma from hostiles and calamities.
靠
God damn!
這是我這輩子聽過的最酷的主意
If that ain't the coolest thing I've ever heard in my life!
不但可行  而且霸氣
Not only is that practical, it is just bad-ass!
看看你  機靈鬼博士
Look at you, Dr. Smarty-pants.
瑞克有沒有讓你替他做這些有意義的事
Did Rick have you doing this kind of valuable stuff for him?
他虧了  我們賺了
His loss, our gain.
我覺得應該給你簽約獎金
I feel like I need to give you some kind of signing bonus here.
我已經得到了腌黃瓜
Uh, w-well, I wa-- I was gifted these pickles.
不
No.
作為對你的答謝
As a token of my gratitude,
我要送我的老婆們
I'm gonna send you over a few of my wives
到你房間去  讓你樂一樂
to your apartment tonight, show you a good time.
現在我不用擔心這事了
Now, I don't think I have to worry about this.
但誰又知道你到底有多聰明呢
But who knows how truly smart you are?
不準上床
No sex.
那是禁區
That is a grave no-no.
但你可以吃頓愜意的晚餐
However, you can have a little dinner,
喝喝小酒  樂呵樂呵
some drinks, share a few laughs.
沒什么比漂亮妞的體香
There is nothing like beautiful women that smell good
更讓你覺得自己又像個人了
to make you feel human again.
這方面我完全不了解
I wouldn't know anything about that.
你剛才說"老婆們"  是指有很多嗎
D-d-did you say "Wives", meaning plural?
正是
Hell yes, I did.
機靈鬼博士要對
What does Dr. Smarty-pants say
他在世界上最好的新朋友說什么嗎
to his new bestest friend in the whole wide world?
要說什么嗎
What does he say?
謝謝
Thank you.
非常地  完全地
Fully, completely...
誠心地  認真地感謝你
Sincerely, seriously...Thank you.
好吧
Okay.
去找點樂子吧
Why don't you go have some fun?
這是什么鬼東西
What the hell am I even looking at?
類似小蟲子的生物叫亞爾
The insect-like creature is called Yar.
它們試圖報復
It is attempting to exact revenge
惡魔昆塔  因為它摧毀了拉扎克四
upon the evil Qotile for the destruction of Razak IV.
也許你該放松點  安珀
Maybe you should take it easy, Amber.
也許我不應該  弗蘭基
Maybe I shouldn't, Frankie.
我們可以玩點別的
Uh, we could play something else.
戰神
Warlords?
可以四個人玩  很有趣
It's four-player and quite the hoot.
你想玩什么都行
Whatever you want.
今晚為你服務
This is your night.
想來個按摩嗎
Do you want a massage?
尼根很喜歡
Negan loves them.
我是認證按摩師
And I was a licensed therapist.
以前是
You know, before.
感謝你的好意
While I appreciate the gesture
還有你對指定對象的認真精神
and your commitment to your assigned objective,
我非常清楚今晚你們沒有一位是
I am fully aware that none of you ladies are here this evening
出于自愿來的
of your own volition.
電子游戲是我唯一可以展示給你們的樂子
Video games are all about me showing all of you a fun time.
還想再吃點微波爐爆米花嗎
Would you care for more microwave popcorn?
雖然這是尼根的主意
Hey, just because this was Negan's idea
但不意味著我們不愿意來
doesn't mean that we don't want to be here.
只要有理性談話  我就愿意來
I'd be down with just having an intelligent conversation.
我想在目前的情況下
Well, I suppose a conversation would be acceptable
談話是可以接受的
under the current circumstance.
你們想談什么
What would you like to talk about?
人類基因組計劃怎么樣
Uh, how about the human genome project?
我可以聊一整晚這玩意
I could talk about that shit all night.
說實話
In truth...
我在人類基因組計劃中的主要工作
The bulk of my work for the HGP
屬于黑盒子項目的一部分
fell under the auspices of the black box program,
而我無權談論此事
of which I am not at liberty to discuss.
就算我可以
In all likelihood, even if I could,
你們也很可能無法理解
it'd probably escape your comprehension.
他剛侮辱了我們嗎  塔尼婭
Did he just insult us, Tanya?
這不是侮辱
It was not a dis.
僅僅是陳述事實
It was simply a statement of fact.
我的智商經歷過客觀測量
My intelligence has been objectively measured.
我是個鶴立雞群的人
I am fully a man apart.
那你就是那種能用漂白劑
So, what, are you, like, one of those guys who can make a bomb
和牙簽什么的做炸彈的人咯
out of bleach and a toothpick or something?
當然不是
Of course not.
那至少需要干酵母  過氧化氫
That would at least require dry yeast, hydrogen peroxide,
少量洗潔精
and a small amount of liquid dish soap,
也許還要一些潔廁靈或者通渠劑
maybe some, you know, bathroom or drain cleaner,
一些氣球之類的
some balloons or something like that,
再加一些常見的生活用品
few other common household sundries.
真的嗎
Seriously?
千真萬確
Serious as sepsis.
真的嗎
Seriously?
真蠢
So stupid.
我希望這能展現我的聰明
I'm hoping to illustrate the opposite.
只是奴隸嗎
Just slaves?
你說什么
Excuse me?
隨便了
Whatever.
尤金博士  你剛用廁所里的東西制造了氦氣嗎
Dr. Eugene, did you just make helium out of toilet stuff?
是氫氣
Hydrogen.
沒事  基諾
It's cool, Keno.
我們沒事
We're good.
放松
Relax.
你是我們中的一員了
You're one of us.
我應該提前說明
I should disclose in advance
我將其歸類為炸彈也許是有點說大話
I may have oversold this one by classifying it as a bomb.
過氧化氫分解時
As the hydrogen peroxide decomposes,
這一反應會以放熱的形式釋放能量
the reaction will release energy in the form of heat.
尤金博士  你能給我們看點精彩的嗎
Dr. Eugene, can you please just show us some good shit?
我要點燃這根蠟燭
I'm gonna light this candle.
-真酷  -終于
- Cool! - Finally.
不  我是說  我要點燃這根蠟燭
No, I mean, I'm gonna light this candle.
不
Oh, no.
耶
Yay!
好棒
Yeah!
親愛的
Honey?
D  我們總是說如果我們分開了
D -- we always said that if we got separated,
我應該回到這里等你
I should come back here and wait for you.
你會帶著啤酒和椒鹽脆餅出現
You'd show up with beer and pretzels.
記得嗎
You remember that?
我知道
I know.
你也許不記得了
You probably don't.
你總說我們開始約會時
You always said that when we started dating,
你忘記告訴我你記性很差了
you forgot to tell me you had a shitty memory.
你以前會因此很沮喪
You used to get so frustrated by it...
知道你不會記得那些好時光
knowing you wouldn't remember those good days...
特別的日子
those special days.
喂金魚  愛你的雪莉
快走
我為你感到難過
I felt bad for you.
我記得你說過
I remember you said
你有許多想記住的事
there was so much you wanted to hold on to,
但你就這樣忘了
and then it'd be gone.
但你很幸運你記性不好  D
But you're lucky you don't remember things, D.
真希望我現在能等你
I wish I could wait for you now.
但我不知道你會跟我走
But I don't know if you'd come with me
還是帶我回去
Or if you'd take me back there
還是殺了我
Or you'd kill me.
你不想活在那個世界里
You didn't want to live in that world,
是我逼你的
and I made you.
我那樣做是因為我不想讓你死
I did what I did because I didn't want you to die.
但現在你殺人了
But now you've killed,
成為了你不想成為的人
and you've become everything you didn't want to be,
這是我的錯
And it's my fault.
你比我更好
You were better than me.
大部分人都是
Most people are.
我放達里爾走
I let Daryl go
因為他讓你想起了以前的自己
Because he reminded you of who you used to be.
而我想讓你忘掉
And I wanted to let you forget.
我不覺得自己能在外面活下去
I don't think I'm gonna make it out here,
但你錯了
but you're wrong.
在那里并不比死了更好
Being there isn't better than being dead.
而是更糟
It's worse.
我希望你能明白
I hope you realize that,
希望你能離開那
and I hope you get away.
我希望你記得那些美好的時光
I hope you remember the good days,
哪怕只記得一點  但是...
even just one of them, but...
我不認為你會想起來
I don't think you will.
你也許根本不會讀到這封信
I don't think you'll ever read this.
我愛以前的你
I loved who you were.
很抱歉  我讓你變成了現在這樣
I'm sorry I made you into who you are.
再見
Goodbye.
親愛的
Honey.
我們聽到你在玩亞爾和昆塔了  尤金
We can hear the Yars and the Qotile, Eugene.
在我的理解里  昨晚的事情
I was given to understand that last night's shinny
應該是單一偶發事件
was supposed to be a singular incident.
不是他叫我們來的
He didn't send us.
我們需要你的幫助
We need your help.
昨晚你看到安珀的樣子了
You saw Amber last night.
喝了哭  哭了喝
She just drinks and cries.
她不想做這個
She didn't want this.
我們是自愿的
We signed up for it.
對我們來說更好
It's better for us.
她是被迫的
She had to.
她媽媽需要藥
Her mom needed meds.
她又不能干活
She can't work.
安珀本以為
Amber thought...
她可以忍受
that she could live with it.
她做不到
She can't.
她求我們幫她結束這一切
She asked us to help her end it.
你們沒有什么
You aren't afforded any...
心理健康輔導可做嗎
mental-health services?
沒有
No.
-你是認真的嗎  -你們有認證女按摩師
- Are you serious? - I mean, there's a licensed masseuse here.
按概率來說  應該...
Uh, odds being what they are --
沒有那樣的人
There's no one like that here.
只能這樣了
So this...is it.
她只是想吃點什么
She just wants to take something.
睡過去  再不醒過來
She wants to go to sleep and not wake up.
那樣非常不負責任
That would be wildly irresponsible.
她在睡夢中死去
She dies at night, in her sleep,
變成行尸的時候  其他人都在睡覺
she turns while everyone is asleep...
我們負責處理那部分
We'll handle that part.
我們希望你能幫她做點什么
We were hoping that you could make something for her,
因為我們知道你會做東西
'cause we know that you can make things.
我知道這很瘋狂  你也不怎么了解我們
Look, I know that this is crazy and you barely know us...
但是我們知道你是個好人
But we can tell that you are a good man.
現在好人不多了
There aren't many of those left.
事實上  我不是好人
Truth of the matter is, I'm not good.
我不守序  不中立  不叛逆
I'm not lawful, neutral, or chaotic --
《龍與地下城》中道德倫理體系
以上都不是
None of the above.
你是說你不會做是嗎
Are you saying you can't do it?
并不是能力缺失的問題
Lack of ability is not the problem here.
我可以用現有的材料
I could jerry-rig a lethal toxin
隨意提取出某種致命毒素
with the assets at hand here.
-沒問題  我是...  -那就幫幫我們
- No problemo. I have the -- - Then help us.
一片藥  一小杯藥水  都可以
A pill, a shot, whatever.
我們需要兩份
We need two of them.
因為我們不知道什么時候才有機會
'cause we don't know when we could get our chance.
無論我們幫不幫她  她都要尋死的
She's gonna do it, with or without us.
她會很痛苦  或者導致其他人受傷
She'll suffer, and maybe someone else will get hurt.
你是好人  尤金
You are good, Eugene.
你一定要是
You have to be.
她有多重
How much does she weigh?
不知道  一百二吧
Don't know. Maybe...120.
怎么了
Why?
如果你們能告訴我她的準確體重
If you could get me her exact weight,
我可以保證做出半精加工無痛毒藥
I could guarantee a semi-precise t.O. Pain-free d.
盡快做出
A.S.A.P.
目前只能這樣了
Best I can do for now.
晚點再來吧
Come back later.
我們幾個人玩撲克
We're playing poker with some guys.
試著幫你牽線
Try to hook you up.
你在開玩笑嗎  玩不了撲克了
You kidding? Can't play poker.
明天早上天一亮
I got to be out diggin' postholes
我就得出去挖坑
at the crack of dawn tomorrow.
我需要一板鋁塑包裝的
I would like a single blister pack
最強效的感冒膠囊
of your most extra-strength cold capsule.
隊是用來排的
The line's a line!
怎么  你老家都不排隊嗎
What, they not have them where you come from?
你不知道怎么排嗎
You don't know how they work?
不  我熟悉...
No, I am familiar --
后面排著去  混蛋
Get in it, prick.
你的編號是多少
What is your number?
你的呢
What's yours?
16.
好吧  16號
All right, number 16.
我是尤金·波特博士
My name is Dr. Eugene Porter.
我最近被授予了
I've recently been appointed
這里新設立的首席工程師之職
to the newly created post of chief engineer of this facility.
我直屬尼根管理
I report directly to Negan,
這意味著你直屬我管理
which means you report directly to my ass.
我要感冒膠囊  快點
The cold capsules, now.
我不知道
I didn't know.
只是  來的新人很多...
We just -- we get so many new faces, I didn't...
這個我也要
I want this, too.
還有這個
And this.
我不知道你管這叫什么
I don't even know what you call this.
我要叫它小黏糊
I'm gonna call it a gremblygunk.
你找到她了嗎
Did you find her?
她在哪
Where is she?
我殺了她
I killed her.
她逃向了一群行尸中
She ran away from me right into a mess of dead ones,
所以我...給了她痛快
So, I, uh... Made it quick.
還是會痛
It still hurts.
有繃帶好一些
Feels better with a bandage.
我不是說這個
I wasn't talking about that.
我本想告訴你忘了她  但是...
I would tell you to just forget about her, but...
考慮到她做的事情  我不覺得短時間內
...I don't see anyone else doing that anytime soon,
會有人這么做
considering what she did.
我們都做過一些事情
Oh, we've all done things.
是的  但在我們來這里之前
Yes, but before we got here,
在我們懂得之前
Before we understood...
我們像個懦夫
We were cowards about it.
我們...不能留有善良之心
We don't -- we don't get to have big hearts.
記住這一點
Remember that.
這是干什么
Wh-what is this?
你會知道的
You'll find out.
你最好睜眼好好看著
You are gonna want to pay close attention to this.
不
no, no, no, no!
為什么
Why?
我什么都沒做
I didn't do anything.
我發現這個小紀念品
I found this little souvenir
藏在你的桌子里
tucked away in your desk.
再見  親愛的
我不知道那是什么
I-I-I don't know what that is.
你
You...
開門放走了我的寵物
left the door open and let my puppy out.
你知道雪莉不希望達里爾在這里
You knew Sherry hated Daryl being here,
所以你為她放了他  趁機逞英雄
So you let him out for her, be the hero.
然后你就可以插一腳了
Then you could move in.
你...
That...
真夠狡猾
is some weaselly shit right there.
我沒這么做  是她自己逃跑的...
But I didn't. She's the one who ran --
她逃跑
Oh, she ran?
你知道為什么她會逃嗎
You know why she ran?!
因為她知道我會怪她
Because she knew I would blame her, which...
確實如此
I did.
但是雪莉在她被撕碎之前
But, see, Sherry told Dwighty boy the whole story
告訴了小德整件事的經過
right before she was torn apart.
一個超級辣妹  因為你的
A super hot girl, horrifically killed
癡心妄想和小雞雞
Because of your greedy, delusional,
被殘忍殺死
and tiny little prick.
這不是真的  德懷特
It's not true. Dwight?
他在撒謊
He's lying about it.
-我決不會這么做  -為什么
- I would never do that. - Why?
為什么  為什么他要撒謊呢
Why? Why would he do that?
為什么他要故意傷害你呢
Why would he intentionally try to hurt you?
雪莉死了
Sherry's gone.
如果他撒了謊
And if he's lying...
她還活著  我會找到她
And she's out there, I will find her.
然后我會燒了他另外半張臉
And then I will burn the other side of his face off
直到他死
until he dies.
他能從中得到什么好處呢
So, what was he gonna get out of this?
不
No.
我了解我的小德
You see, I know my Dwighty boy.
他需要的只是
See, all he needed...
在牢房里再被關一晚
was one more night in the hole,
然后腦子就正常了
get his head screwed on straight.
以前管用  現在也管用
It worked before, and it worked now.
是不是啊  德懷特
Ain't that right, Dwight?
是的
Oh, yeah.
求求你
oh, please.
不  求求你
No, please.
求求你
Please, please, please!
天啊  不要燙我
Oh, jesus, don't burn me.
求求你
Please!
不
No.
不  求求你
No, no, please!
你知道我討厭這樣做
Now you know I hate this shit.
只用告訴我是你做的  你很抱歉
Just tell me you did it and that you're sorry,
我就不用動手了
And I don't have to do this.
是的
Yes.
是我做的  都是我做的
Yes, I did it -- all of it.
抱歉  我很抱歉
Sorry. I'm so sorry.
求求你
Please...
抱歉
I'm sorry.
這么說就行了
That's all you had to say.
That is all you had to say.
幸好我們還有個卡森醫生
A good thing we got a spare Dr. Carson.
我相信你  小德
I trust you, Dwighty boy.
從來不該懷疑你
Never shoulda doubted you.
雪莉是我最喜歡的女人之一
Sherry was one of my favorites.
我很遺憾
I'm sorry.
我不
I'm not.
冷血
Ice-cold.
我喜歡
I love it.
進
Come.
你好
Hello.
你還好嗎
Are you all right?
挺好的
Better than that.
你可以下局玩  不過要等一會
You can call next, but it might be a while.
你做藥了嗎
Did you make the pills?
做了
I did.
但不能給你們
But you can't have them.
安珀指望著我們呢
Amber's counting on us.
我們跟她說你會幫助我們
We told her that you were gonna help us,
-她說她...  -住嘴  紅發
- and she says that she -- - Pump your brakes, red.
別侮辱我的智商  弗蘭基
Do not insult my intelligence, Frankie.
藥不是給安珀的
Said pills aren't for Amber.
藥是給尼根的
Said pills are for Negan.
所以你要兩份
That's why you wanted two.
他不是殺了你的朋友們嗎
Didn't he kill your friends?
殺了好幾個
Several.
但我們也殺了他的三十多個人
But I imagine we killed about 30 or so of his.
扯平了
Turnabout and all that.
給我們藥  不然我們給尼根告狀
Give us the pills, or we'll tell Negan about it.
我們會說做藥是你的主意
We'll tell him that it was your idea to make them
你試圖勸我們協助你
and that you tried to get us to help.
那會是你的戰術錯誤
That would be a tactical error on your part.
他會信我而不是你
They'll believe me over you
正如他信德懷特而不是醫生一樣
for the same reason he believed Dwight over the doctor.
你對他來說是可取代的
You're replaceable to him.
另一方面  我則不是
I, on the other hand, am not.
你是個懦夫
You're a coward.
你是個...懦夫
You're...a coward.
這是正確的評價
That is a correct assessment.
我能進來嗎
May I come in?
你喜歡這里嗎
So, how you liking it here?
我們把機靈鬼博士招待得好嗎
Are we doing right by Dr. Smarty-pants?
弗蘭基和塔尼婭
You know, Frankie and Tanya...
她們說的都是你的好話
Nothing but good things to say about you.
沒關系
It's all right.
我明白
I get it.
我知道接受改變
I know how hard it can be to accept change,
棄暗投明有多難
to get on the right team.
但是我需要你明白一些事
But I need you to understand something.
我不會隨意邀請他人
I do not make this invitation to everyone.
我的邀請分量也很重
And I sure as shit do not make it lightly.
你不用再害怕了
You do not need to be scared anymore.
你不用害怕了
You don't need to be scared.
只用回答我一個問題
You just have to answer me one question.
這是個大問題
And it's a big one.
你是...
Who are --
我是尼根
I'm Negan.
我完完全全  徹頭徹尾是尼根
I'm utterly, completely, stone-cold Negan.
遇見你之前我就是尼根了
I was Negan before I even met you.
遇見你之后  我才醒悟
I just needed to meet you properly to know.
我是尼根
I'm Negan.
當心點
Hey, be careful with that.
你想被熔態金屬燙到嗎
Hey, you want to get burned by molten metal?
因為那樣做會被熔態金屬燙到的
'cause that's exactly how you get burned by molten metal.
關于我施壓...
Regarding me clamping down --
你跟我們一伙嗎
You on board?
是的  和你一樣
I am. Just like you.
-不知道你是否記得我名字  -不記得
Don't know if you recall my handle -- I don't.
尤金
Eugene.
你是德懷特
You're Dwight.
我們都是尼根
We are Negan.
是啊
Yeah.